{
    "subject": "resource/Sara_Guasch",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Mexico",
    "human_readable": "Sara Guasch died in Mexico.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9302336573600769,
            "question": "Was Sara Guasch from Mexico?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8935480117797852,
            "question": "Where did Sara Guasch die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.873145580291748,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in Mexico at the time of Sara Guasch's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7412881255149841,
            "question": "What was the cause of Sara Guasch's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7280214428901672,
            "question": "Are there any other details about Sara Guasch's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5101310610771179,
            "question": "Is there a historical context surrounding Sara Guasch's life and death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3920063078403473,
            "question": "What is known about Sara Guasch's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2610228359699249,
            "question": "Can you find any biographies or records related to Sara Guasch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2584803104400635,
            "question": "Is there information available about Sara Guasch's profession or background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10562849789857864,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Mexico?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sara Guasch died in Mexico.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3432_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there information available about Sara Guasch's profession or background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3432_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you find any biographies or records related to Sara Guasch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3432_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Sara Guasch's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3432_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3432_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe documents state that Sara Guasch died on June 1, 2005, in Mexico, Distrito Federal, Mexico. This supports the statement \"Sara Guasch died in Mexico.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}